#### Способы связаться

fourhtyoz@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/boristatarenko (LinkedIn)

### Основные навыки

Python

Django

Flask

### Languages

German (Full Professional)
Spanish (Full Professional)
Turkish (Professional Working)
English (Full Professional)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)

# **Boris Tatarenko**

Software Engineer / Full-Stack Developer Москва, Москва, Россия

# Общие сведения

Despite majoring in a not-very-down-to-Earth field, I decided to study finance, investments, stocks and global markets to become a professional financial analyst.

Working as a business analyst and an asset manager handling multiple European (German, Spanish, British, Turkish) companies and 10 million USD assets allowed me to develop both soft and hard skills: teamwork, business communication, business ethics, networkring along with advanced Excel skills, financial modelling and group management. My previous work experience allowed me to live in various countries (Malta, UAE, Turkey).

Although I'm no longer looking for new career opportunities in finance, I'm glad I've tried the path and I've been lucky enough to gain such crazy hands-on experience and meet new people to broaden my worldview.

It took me several years to realize what field I'd genuinely like to build a prosperous career in: software engineering and web development. The world of IT is what truly attracts and fascinantes me, especially, how vast it is and what opportunities it has to offer.

Learning and equipping yourself with a totally new skillset, obviously, take a decent amount of time but the bitter -- and sweet -- truth is learning never ends. With a motto like this in my mind, I've embarked on a new career.

General skillset: English, German, Spanish and Turkish, business communication, Excel, VB.

Current IT skillset: Python (Backend, Selenium, WebSockets, RegEx), Django, Flask, HTML5, CSS3, JS (Frontend), SQL. Also I'm going to learn: JS (Angular, React, Vue, Node.js), Go, Ruby (Ruby on Rails), C and C#.

Furthermore, I'm interested in (on par with full-stack development) ML, AI, robotics, open-source, cloud computing, game development (Unity), hackathons, computer science and solving problems on LeetCode.

For more information:

https://www.github.com/fourhtyoz/ https://www.fourhtyoz.github.io/

# Опыт работы

Guta Group Senior Analyst сентября 2019 - Present (3 года 1 месяц)

Москва, Россия

- Writing financial reports
- Building financial models
- Managing teams remotely and on-site
- Controlling 10 million USD assets
- Business communication with partners, subsidiaries, authorities
- Managing court cases
- Filling tax declarations

#### Deloitte

Audit Assistant сентября 2019 (1 год 1 месяц)

Moscow, Moscow City, Russia

- Working with companies and government agencies to research and solve problems and develop policies and procedures that comply with current legislation
- Analyzing, evaluating, developing, and implementing new control systems
- Recording, reviewing, and interpreting financial data
- Researching discrepancies, operational problems, or other issues
- Examining records, reports, receipts etc and comparing them to company assets and liabilities
- Bringing company strengths and weaknesses to the attention of management and providing advice
- Generating reports and presenting findings to management or other interested parties

# Фриланс

## Interpreter

сентября 2017 - сентября 2018 (1 год 1 месяц)

- English-Russian translations (medicine)
- Russian-English translations (medicine)
- Transalting iOS and Adroid apps into Russian (lifestyle, sport, medicine)

# Образование

Московский Государственный Институт Международных Отношений (Университет) МИД России (МГИМО)

· (2014 - 2018)

### Freie Universität Berlin

Bachelor's degree, Internationale Beziehungen · (сентября 2016 - сентября 2017)